

Ghaith Al-Refaee

Software developer

i have 25 years old, I am a professional back-end developer with experience in managing and resolving technical issues related to computers and networks. I specialize in programming, application development, and website development, delivering efficient and scalable solutions.

- ✓ ghisoor@gmail.com
- Abu Dhabi, Damascus, Syria
- facebook.com/Ghaith Rifai
- (instagram.com/Ghaith Rifai

+971557874058

SKILLS

Mikrotik

- in linkedin.com/in/Ghaith Al-Refae
- github.com/ghith-refae

WORK EXPERIENCE

System developer

Izone solution 01/2019 - 12/2020

Damascus-Syria

is an IT outsourcing company delivers customer-service. IZONE Technology Response Team is a real partner in your business technology.

Help desk ISP Inet

01/2021 - 07/2021 Damascus-Syria
One of the leading Internet Service Providers in Syria.

Achievements/Tasks

Technical support

Freelancer

Remote task system

Achievements/Tasks

 Application development, and website development, delivering efficient and scalable solutions.

ACHIEVEMENTS

IZONE SOLUUION

Successfully repaired and optimized the surveillance camera system at Al-Sham Private University, ensuring enhanced security and seamless operation across the campus

Adobe Xd

android studio

LANGUAGES

EN AF

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

EDUCATION

Bachelor degree of communication tech Syrian virtual university

01/2019 - Present

Courses

 I have 5classes remaining to complete my degree.
 with the option to skip attendance due to my experience.

Technical Institute for Computer Science.

Damascus University

01/2019 - 01/2022